{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:73..973.off100.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256500934","data":{"timestamp":" 947256500934"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" 70e326e8-3f5a-4c29-93a6-7ad565a3fc7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256527241","data":{"timestamp":" 947256527240"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" 70e326e8-3f5a-4c29-93a6-7ad565a3fc7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256533118","data":{"timestamp":" 947256533118"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" 70e326e8-3f5a-4c29-93a6-7ad565a3fc7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.read::story_79","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256539267","data":{"timestamp":" 947256539267"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" 70e326e8-3f5a-4c29-93a6-7ad565a3fc7f"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.read__story_79"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hakuna aliyekuwa na chakula isipokuwa kunguru."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256555838","data":{"timestamp":" 947256555838"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" ce712848-b7b4-49f1-860b-f8392345f896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_594_594-211-375"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 594"," userResponse":" 375"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256574308","data":{"timestamp":" 947256574308"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" ce712848-b7b4-49f1-860b-f8392345f896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_594_594-211-375"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 594"," userResponse":" 594"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256583636","data":{"timestamp":" 947256583636"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" ce712848-b7b4-49f1-860b-f8392345f896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_423_537-385-423"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 423"," userResponse":" 537"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256600925","data":{"timestamp":" 947256600925"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" ce712848-b7b4-49f1-860b-f8392345f896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_423_537-385-423"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 423"," userResponse":" 423"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256617320","data":{"timestamp":" 947256617320"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" ce712848-b7b4-49f1-860b-f8392345f896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_715_320-715-437"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 715"," userResponse":" 715"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256626750","data":{"timestamp":" 947256626750"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" ce712848-b7b4-49f1-860b-f8392345f896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_596_481-596-437"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 596"," userResponse":" 596"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256645748","data":{"timestamp":" 947256645748"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" ce712848-b7b4-49f1-860b-f8392345f896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_607_288-389-607"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 607"," userResponse":" 607"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256661167","data":{"timestamp":" 947256661167"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" ce712848-b7b4-49f1-860b-f8392345f896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_368_368-523-572"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 368"," userResponse":" 572"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256676144","data":{"timestamp":" 947256676144"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" ce712848-b7b4-49f1-860b-f8392345f896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_368_368-523-572"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 368"," userResponse":" 523"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256692024","data":{"timestamp":" 947256692024"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" ce712848-b7b4-49f1-860b-f8392345f896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_368_368-523-572"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 368"," userResponse":" 368"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256750266","data":{"timestamp":" 947256750265"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" ce712848-b7b4-49f1-860b-f8392345f896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_735_233-356-735"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 735"," userResponse":" 735"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947256754990","data":{"timestamp":" 947256754990"," userId":" 6111002083"," sessionId":" 6111002083_20000107_174723"," gameId":" ce712848-b7b4-49f1-860b-f8392345f896"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_100..900.MN-TD-UP-OFF100-BL3.incr.82"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_735_233-356-735"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}